Prateek Srivastava

MERN Full-stack Developer

Contact Info

+91 9565973316

Personal Info

Dedicated and efficient full stack developer (MERN) with 1+ years of experience in application layers, presentation layers, and databases.

Certified in both F/E and B/E technologies. Have experience in AWS elastic beanstalk and route53. Seeking to further improve React and MongoDB skills as a full stack developer.

Skills

MongoDB ExpressJS NodeJS

React Native ReactJS C++

AWS Elastic Beanstalk AWS Route 53

C (Programming language) Python

Other skills

Git & Github Team Management Linux

Hobbies









Playing Guitar



Experience

React-Native Developer

01/2022 - 06/2022

- · Completed internship in react-native.
- Integrated API calls, implemented login and other features.

Full-Stack Developer

09/2021 - 01/2022

- · Maintaining and adding to the backend
- · Maintaing deployment using elastic beanstalk
- · Core full stack engineer at a startup

Backend Developer

06/2021 - 09/2021

- Created backend of more than three applications at several startups
- · With database management in MongoDB
- · Deployed on AWS elastic beanstalk
- · Uploaded apps on google playstore

Education

Bachelor of Technology

2020 - 2024

- · AKGEC, Ghaziabad
- Member of Team Oorja-the technical society
- College football team player

Intermediate

2019

- · SGPS (affiliated by CBSE)
- Passed with aggregate percentage of 91.6%

High School

2017

- SGPS (affiliated by CBSE)
- Passed with aggregate CGPA of 9.2

Follow Me

https://www.linkedin.com/in/prateek-srivastav-4a91a5220

https://github.com/Prateek-Srivastav